http://www.splicit.com/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
Privacy Policy
We understand that your privacy is very important to you.
We are committed to safeguarding your personal information.
The following is a summary of what information we collect from you and how that information is used.What information do we collect?
We obtain personal information from you such as name, e-mail, phone number, address, credit card information, etc. when you register on our site or place an order.
We also obtain information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase.
None of the information we obtain is used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to make your shopping experience more enjoyable and gather information about which pages you have visited on our website. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you the following ways:
To send you updates about your order and announcements about new and exciting products that we are offering that may be of interest to you.
To fulfill your order and allow you to review your order history and to facilitate easier reordering with us.
If we have trouble processing your order we'll use this information to contact you.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails.
How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?At no time will we provide any information you provide to any outside sources or companies and we will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. The term "outside parties" does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and/or for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
This policy was last modified on March 10, 2016.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
